
LabVIEW drivers 32-bit only
Nexus Conditioning Amplifiers Types 2690, 2691, 2692, 2693
This release covers all Nexus Conditioning Amplifiers Types 2690, 2691, 2692, 2693 containing hardware version 2.0 or greater. It requires Nexus Control Software Type 7749 version 1.1 or greater.

Disclaimer: This driver is not currently supported and is provided as is.


Type 7749 and BZ-5291 are PC-based software packages for set-up and control of the NEXUS, Types 2690-2693, and Type 2694 ranges of conditioning amplifiers.

Version 2 of the software adds support for Microsoft Windows 7 (x32 or x64). Also, both programs are now included in one installation program. 



___________________________________________________________________________________________

Introduction

This file contains last minute information about the NEXUS Setup & Control software version 2.0

There are two sections:

    Version 2.0
    Known Problems

Version 2.0

This version of the software will now run on Windows® XP, Windows® 7 (32-bit and 64-bit).

Known Problems

COM Port Problems on Computers with Internal Modems

Problem

The software does not respond or it takes several minutes after selecting a COM port before the software responds.

Cause

Some computers, like laptop computers, have devices installed such as modems. These devices and their associated software can add more COM ports to the system than physically exist.

Workaround

    Use Windows® Task Manager to end the NEXUS Setup & Control software Type 7749 application.
    Restart the NEXUS Setup & Control software and avoid selection of the port that causes the problem. Select another COM port, that works.
    If you do not know which COM port is active, we suggest to try one COM Port at a time.
